Thank you for watching.
Good morning.
Today is the first day of our 36th single under live national tour!
I'm going to tell you how I'm spending the day of the live.
I'm going to tell you how I'm spending the day today.
Here you go!
Good morning!
Good morning
Let me introduce you
It's okay, I'm here
I want to debut on YouTube
I want to make my debut.
I'm Ms. Komori.
I see you've arrived recently.
He's an owl.
He's an owl?
A little bat-like.
It's like horns.
It's a Biran type of stitching.
It's a stuffed animal.
That's a new one.
It's different.
The bird series has been expanded.
Nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you.
I'll brush my teeth.
After-the-fact report.
I don't know if I can do this.
I'm brushing my teeth.
No, you might get tired.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I can do it.
Oh, I'm getting naughty now.
Tomi.
Don't be naughty, Tomi.
No?
She says, "It's Tomi.
She says hello again today.
I'm wearing a costume.
It's a new one.
We're going to rehearse in it.
Rehearsal is over.
What do you think?
I'm nervous because today we're going to play a song that I'm going to feature.
I'm going to eat my lunch.
You see?
Bon appétit.
I'm glad you're wearing cod roe.
Can you do it?
A lesser version.
Oh, this one.
Oh, my God.
A little bit.
More version.
I think it's okay to have more today, but...
I'll do it this way
I'm going to do this.
I'm going to prepare a photo to put on Instagram.
He said it's hard because he doesn't have any sense of style.
So I've been working on this for two minutes.
It's done!
He's so confused about colors and sizes, so it's hard to make it.
Then I'll send it to you.
It's 20 minutes ago. 20 minutes to go.
Okay, I'll show you something pretty.
Yes, oh, he's here.
Hello.
Mayim, I don't know what to do. I'm so nervous.
It's so aggressive.
It's pretty strong, actually.
Which is bad?
It's just to get me pumped up. I'll do my best.
You're injecting it into me.
It's new.
I've met some new people.
Members?
Finally, the first day of UnderLive has arrived!
I'm getting nervous just now.
Everyone is so cute today!
I'm so happy!
Let's enjoy the show with confidence!
Seino
Giggle, giggle, giggle, giggle, giggle!
Thanks for your hard work and smiling faces!
Thank you very much for your support!
Encore!
It's too early!
The show's already over.
But you know what?
We can't do an encore.
Let's go.
Let's go, guys.
Let's go, let's go.
Let's go, everybody.
Encore.
22 years old, living for this meeting
I'll go out there and do my best.
Congratulations!
To today's encore
Thank you very much.
Congratulations!
The blue ring era is
throughout the whole country.
тоб law first
good job чи machin
unlocked
in the first generation
The House of Representatives
elected
plus
became the representative
before Subara
all the way
Professor Renjyu
is
So, the first day in Fukuoka is over!
The first day in Fukuoka is over!
You look like you're done, don't you?
We'll be back tomorrow for the second day.
I'm going to make the best of it.
I'll do my best.
And we're on tour.
We're going to go to a lot of places.
We can still perform.
I'll do my best to bring you a better show.
See you all tomorrow!
Bye bye bye.
I'll do my best.